{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"1799/93",
			"answer":"1799/93",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3294/70",
			"answer":"3294/70",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6753/26",
			"answer":"6753/26",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1158/95",
			"answer":"1158/95",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6219/90",
			"answer":"6219/90",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"443.7/0.87",
			"answer":"443.7/0.87",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.873/0.36",
			"answer":"1.873/0.36",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"24.18/31",
			"answer":"24.18/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.209/0.11",
			"answer":"0.209/0.11",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5.78/0.17",
			"answer":"5.78/0.17",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}